palladiumboots.com 2011-03-15

# Palladium Boots - Customer Service - Privacy/Company Policies

**What Personal Information We Collect**

Palladium and its affiliates (hereafter, "Palladium" or "We") may collect your personal information for various purposes when you visit the Palladiumboots.com website (the "Site"). For example:

_Membership_

If you want to register an account on the site, you will need to provide us with certain contact details and other information about yourself. We want you to know how we limit collection and use of this information and how we restrict the collection of it. These same rules and restrictions apply to all information that you give to us when you place an order on this website. 

_Preferred Customers_

In order to become a Preferred Customer, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to give personal contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to reward loyal customers for their business. By becoming a Preferred Customer, you are able to take advantage of special offers we make available to Preferred Customers about new promotions, fashion trends, etc. It is also more convenient for a Preferred Customer to make purchases online. 

_Orders_

We request information from you on our order form. Here you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers' orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with you. 

**If You Are Under 13 Years Old**

**If you are under 13 years old, please get the consent of your parent or legal guardian before you give us any personal information about yourself by way e-mail or any other Internet means.** Your parents or guardian can send us their consent by e-mail, although we may follow up by phone or other means in some circumstances. They will need to give us their name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number, and any other identifying information that we may request. We need this information in order to verify that they have provided the necessary consent. Your parent or guardian should contact us by using the e-mail address: cs@palladiumboots.com. 

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OLD, DO NOT CONTACT US UNTIL AFTER YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN HAS SENT US AN E-MAIL CONSENTING TO YOUR CONTACT. 

**Palladium Policy on Customer Information**

We do not sell personal information to any third party, nor do we have any plans to do so. However, we may share your personal information with our agents, representatives, service providers and contractors for limited purposes, including but not limited to, fulfilling customer orders; offering certain products and services in connection with this Site; communicating to customers; providing customer service; enhancing and improving customers' shopping experience; administering or facilitating surveys, contests or sweepstakes; offering targeted marketing communications to users; providing a personalized shopping experience; preventing fraud; and completing payment processing. 

Our database of personal information is a valuable asset. Therefore, if we sell or transfer an affiliate, business or line of business, we may transfer personal information used or held by that affiliate or business or used in connection with that line of business to the buyer, so long as the buyer agrees that the personal information we transfer will remain subject to this privacy policy. 

Of course, we may disclose your personal information if you give us permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required to prevent harm or injury (such as product recalls, fraud, claims or other liability), or to comply with legal processes (subpoenas, warrants) or as otherwise required by law. 

By personal information, we mean information that we collect and store in a way that allows us to relate it to you personally or to your family, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing or billing address and phone number. This privacy policy applies only to personal information. We may freely use, disclose or sell information that is not specifically associated with you personally or your family (such as statistics or aggregate information about our customers or website visitors.) 

If our privacy policies change, we will post a notice here, so please check this page regularly. You understand that the privacy policy in effect at any time applies to all personal information held by Palladium, whether or not that privacy policy was in effect when the information was collected. For that reason, we will provide customers with the means to let us know that they want us to delete information about them from our database. You may feel free to contact us for this purpose at cs@palladiumboots.com. You will need to give us your full name and e-mail address. 

**Cookies and Other Computer Information**

When you visit Palladiumboots.com, you may be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of this cookie is to identify you when you visit the Site so that we can enhance and customize your online shopping experience and gather information about your activities at our site that may allow us to provide you with information and offers that we think may be of interest to you. We may also collect other information relating to you, your systems and your visit. All of this information may be associated in our databases with your personal information. 

You can choose to browse on Palladiumboots.com without cookies. (Each browser is different, so check your browser's "Help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) However, without these identifier files you will not be able to take advantage of certain features of the Site. 

We may contract with third parties to provide us with data collection and reporting services regarding our customers' activities on the Site; tracking and measuring performance of our marketing efforts and your response to our marketing efforts; and the delivery of relevant marketing messages. These third parties may use cookies and Web beacons, and may receive information about your browsing and buying activity on the Site. 

**Links to Other Sites**

We may provide links to resources that you find useful or interesting. Any links that we provide will lead you to sites that may operate under different privacy practices. Our visitors are responsible for reviewing the privacy statements for such other websites. You should be aware that their privacy policies may be materially different from ours, or that they may have no privacy policies at all. We have no control over their policies or over their use or disclosure of any information. We are not responsible for any violations by the operator of any site to which we link you of any privacy or other policy. We make no guarantees about any third party sites.
